Hey Ino... you here?
UNOFFICIAL LEAF VILLAGE MASCOT KONORIN
(シカマル)お～い いの いるか？
Yeah? What are you two
doing together?
(いの)なに？
２人揃ってどうしたの？
Remember what Kakashi Sensei
said last time?
こないだ
カカシ先生から言われた あれ➡
I am giving you
a secret mission
覚えてるだろ？
in which you shall each prepare
a congratulatory gift for
((カカシ : キミたちには
ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いを→
Naruto and Hinata's wedding.
(独自に用意するという
極秘任務を与える))
Of course!
And? What about it?
もちろんよ。
で それがどうしたの？
Oh... I thought we'd discuss
what to get them.
ああ 贈り物の打ち合わせを
しようと思ってよ。
Oh, sorry!
I've got something great
picked out already
残念！ あいにく 私もう
めぼしいものは決めてあるし→
and I'm about to go
to the store.
ちょうど そのお店に
行くとこなの。
Which store?
We'll go with you!
No, you aren't!
どこだ？ 俺たちも行く。
ダメよ！
We can't get gifts from
the same store.
You two can think of
something on your own!
お店かぶるのとか ありえない！
Later!
あんたたちは あんたたちで考えて
じゃあね！
kara no kokoro wo terasu mono wa nani?
What brightens up an empty heart?
sakebi tsuzukeru hikari todoku made
I will keep on singing until the light reaches you
falling through the cracks kurayami e ochiteku
Falling through the cracks, Falling into the darkness
anata no sono te o zettai hanasanai
I will never let go of your hand
tell me the story of your life mada michi no tochuu
Tell me the story of your life, We're still on our way
anata o watashi wa zettai akiramenai
I will never give up on you
osaerarenai shoudou nanigenai hibi wa aijyou
Urges I can't suppress, I live for the ordinary days
natsukashii kaze ni furimukeba itsud
When I turn my cheek to a nostalgic wind
emo anata no koe ga suru yo
I always hear your voice
underdog wa wander around
Underdog will Wander around
mawari michi shitemo nigeru yori mashi yo
Even if I take the long way around,
it's better than running away
jibun de jibun o shinjirare nakucha dare wo shinjiru no?
If I can't learn to believe in myself,
then who can I believe in?
hikari ni sono te kazase
Hold up your hand to the light
shining through the clouds kurayami e ochiteku
Shining through the clouds, Falling into the darkness
anata no sono te o zettai hanasanai
I will never let go of your hand
tell me what is on your mind hateshinai yume wo
Tell me what is on your mind,
Chasing the never ending dream
oikake bokura wa zettai akiramenai
We will never give up
kotae no nai jinsei ni kujike sou ni naru kedo
Discouraged by a life without answers, but I...
don’t give it up! keep it up! turn it upside down!
Don't give it up! Keep it up! Turn it upside down!
kokoro wa tsunagatteru yo tatoe tooku hanaretemo
Our hearts will always be connected,
no matter how far apart we may be
tomo ni tomo ni ikiteyukou
Let's share this life together
What are we gonna do?
Excuse me, Miss!
I'd like to get some ice cream
for dessert.
どうしたもんかな。
(チョウジ)店員さん！
What about you, Shikamaru?
None for me.
デザートのアイスクリームちょうだい。
シカマルは？
You sure can eat, though...
いや 俺はいい。
相変わらず よく食うな。
Your appetite hasn't changed
since you were a kid.
But these days,
I've started liking thigh meat,
胃腸だけは
ガキの頃と同じじゃねえか。
as well as meat that's really rare,
でも 最近は もも肉とか→
so I think I'm going towards
more grown-up tastes.
赤身のお肉も
おいしくなってきたから→
So it's your taste buds?
だいぶ 大人になったと思うよ。
Anyway, getting back
to the subject.
舌の問題かよ。
でよ さっきの話なんだが
どうする？
Maybe yuzu sorbet would've
been better than ice cream...
やっぱ アイスより
ゆずシャーベットだったかな？
No! I'm talking about the wedding gift
for Naruto and Hinata!
Oh that.
違ぇよ！
ナルトたちへの結婚祝いの話だ！
Here's your ice cream.
ああ なんだそっちか。
Oh, it's here!
Judging from Ino's attitude,
she'll be no help...
(大蛇丸)アイス お待ちどおさま。
きたきた！
いののやつ あの調子じゃ
力になってくれそうにねえ。
If this keeps going,
we might be the only ones
who can't find a present.
このままじゃ
俺たちだけ 祝いの品を→
What do you mean by "we"?
用意できねえってことも
ありうるぞ。
I've already picked
something out.
俺たちって どういうこと？
僕は もう 決めてるんだけど。
R-Really?!
What are you getting?
ほ… ほんとかよ！
何にするんだ？
I'm thinking about
giving them this.
うん ２人には
これをあげようかと思ってるんだ。
Hey, this is a—!
SATOCHO DINNER GIFT CERTIFICATE
Yup, a gift certificate
for a dinner!
And it's not just for
an average diner!
お前 これって…。
うん お食事券！
It's a gift certificate for
a super-fancy teahouse
しかも ただのお食事券じゃねえ。
that VIPs like
the Hokage go to!
火影クラスのお偉い人しか
行くことのない→
Well, it is a special occasion...
超高級料亭の
お食事券じゃねえか。
What's going on?!
お祝いだからね。
《クッ どういうことだ？
This is Choji...
And he chose the perfect gift!
あのチョウジが選んだものなのに
贈り物としては最高じゃねえか。
Having dinner in a restaurant
you wouldn't normally be able to go to
is special and really memorable
for a couple!
ふだんでは行けないような店で
食事をするというのは→
お祝い感があるし
２人の思い出に強く残る。
Not a lot of gifts would have
as much impact!
And even if this was
for a special occasion...
これほど気のきいた結婚祝いは
なかなかねえ。
Choji's willing to part
with a gift certificate
それに
いくらお祝いだからといって→
to a super-fancy restaurant,
just like that?
あのチョウジが
そんないい店のお食事券を→
Miss, may I have another bowl
of ice cream?
躊躇なく手放すだと？》
店員さん アイスおかわり。
Are you really
the Choji I know?!
It's not just your taste buds
that grew up.
《シカマル : お前は本当に
あのチョウジなのか？
Have you completely
become an adult?
チョウジ お前は舌だけでなく
いったい全体→
What?
どこまで大人びちまうんだ？》
Here's your ice cream.
It just happened to be
a three-for-one special.
(大蛇丸)アイス お待ち。
ちょうどそれ
３名１組だったんだよね。
Why is it three to a group?
Usually a romantic dinner
is for two.
《よりによって なんで
３名１組なんだよ？
You'd think a fancy restaurant
would be aware of that!
普通 恋人同士で２名様だとか
そういうことを→
Choji will tag along
if it's three to a group!
もうちょっと考えろよ 高級料亭。
Shikamaru?
What's wrong, Shikamaru?
３名様だと チョウジが行くだろうが》
It's nothing...
Are you planning to go too?
シカマル？ どうしたの シカマル？
Are you joking?
いや その もしかして
お前も一緒に…。
Even I know better than to tag along
with some newlyweds...
まさか！ いくら僕でも→
R-Right? Of course you would.
さすがに新婚の２人と
一緒なわけないよ。
I was gonna ask the waitress to
seat me at a different table.
だ だよな。 さすがにそれは…。
店員さんに頼んで
僕だけ違う席にしてもらうよ。
So, you ARE going?!
Still, this is not the time
to get on Choji's case.
《行くのかよ！
I still haven't decided on
what to get them.
いや チョウジのことを
とやかく言ってる場合じゃねえ。
問題なのは まだ祝いの品を
何も決めてない この俺だ。
And I can't waste a minute
on deciding.
I'm thinking...
something useful.
一刻も早く決めねえと。
A decorative item would just get
in the way if it's not to their taste.
実用的なものは
お祝いの感じが薄いし→
Flowers or food would
be gone eventually,
飾り物の趣味が合わなきゃ
邪魔になるだけだ。
and it would seem like
a seasonal gift.
花や食べ物なんかの消えものも→
Sending them something
is really risky...
まるでお歳暮や
お中元みたいに見えちまう。
So that leaves... cash!
やっぱり物を贈るのは
リスキーと言わざるをえねえ。
That's not a bad idea.
だとすると… 現金か！
They can get whatever they want,
悪くはねえ。
and it's way better than getting
something they won't use
好きなものを選んで
買うことができるし→
or something that's identical
to someone else's gift.
使わないものや 他の人と
かぶったものを贈るより→
But wait a minute...
よっぽど気がきいてる。
What if I'm the only one
giving them cash?
いや しかし考えてみろ。
It's not a lot, but please accept it!
俺だけが
現金を持っていったら…》
Not good!
Everyone will think I was
the only one too lazy
((少ねえけど とっとけ))
《ダメだ！
to go out and buy a gift and
俺の場合 面倒くさがって
買い物にも行かず→
just gave them cash
without thinking.
何も考えずに
ただカネだけ出したように→
Shikamaru, you okay?
思われちまわねえか？》
U-Uh, yeah... I just felt a chill.
シカマル 大丈夫？
Sorry, did you get cold
from watching me eat
あ ああ ちょっと寒気がな。
ごめん。
all that ice cream?
That's not it...
僕がアイス食べまくるの見てたら
寒くなっちゃった？
I got hot from eating
all that barbecue,
そうじゃねえが…。
so it was just what I needed.
Besides, I'm the kinda guy
who can eat ice cream
焼肉で ほてった体には
ちょうどいいよ。
even if I'm traveling
in snow country!
それに僕は たとえ
雪国を旅していたとしても→
あえて アイスを買って
食べるタイプの男だからね。
My appetite beats
the cold every time.
Damn it, no one can
beat your appetite—
食欲は 寒さを凌駕するんだ。
まったく お前の食欲には
ついていけね…。
Choji! What did you just say?!
My appetite beats the cold?
チョウジ お前 今 なんて言った？
No, before that!
食欲は寒さを凌駕するって。
What about snow country?
Oh...
違う その前だ！ 雪国を…。
I can eat ice cream even if
I'm traveling in snow country...
あ～ 雪国を旅していても
アイスを食べるって。
That's it!
Steam and                  Food Pills
それだ！
A honeymoon?
Yeah... I'm gonna gift Naruto
and Hinata a honeymoon.
新婚旅行？
ああ ナルトとヒナタに
新婚旅行をプレゼントするんだ。
So where are you off to now?
I have to decide on a place,
and go check it out.
で これからどこへ行くの？
旅先を決めて できれば
下見まで済ましておきてえな。
And I need to get
a woman's point of view
so I can get a sense of
what Hinata might like.
それと ヒナタのことを考えると→
女の目線での意見も
聞いておきてえ。
If only Ino were here...
There she is!
いのでもいれば いいんだが。
いた！
H-Hey...
え？
(テマリ)あ…。
It's been awhile...
ever since that day, huh?
よ よう 久しぶりだな。
あんとき以来か。
Y-Yeah.
What are you guys up to?
あ ああ お前たちこそ
何をしているんだ？
Uh, stuff... We just had
some lunch. And you?
ちょ ちょっとな ２人で昼メシを…
お前は？
I'm here to discuss
the Chunin Exams
わ 私は中忍試験の
打ち合わせついでに→
and making my rounds
to people...
O-Oh... that so?
挨拶回りといったところだ。
お おお そうか。
What the hell?!
I thought you meant
Ino was there...
な なんだよ 「いた！」って
俺は てっきり いのかと。
You said
a "woman's point of view,"
so it doesn't have to be Ino.
でも 女の子の意見っていうなら→
But she's a warrior-type
to the core.
べつに いのじゃなくても
いいじゃない。
I can't talk to her about
a wedding gift...
しかし あいつは
根っからの武闘派だぞ。
What?
結婚祝いの話なんかしたら…。
A honeymoon as
a wedding gift?
((なに？
結婚祝いに新婚旅行？
Talk about a silly
and pathetic idea.
(のん気でくだらないことを
考えてるんだな))
I just know she'd say
something like that.
な～んて返ってくるのは
目に見えてんだろうが。
Wouldn't that apply
to Ino as well?
Hey, what're you two
whispering about?
そんなこと言ったら
いのだって怪しいもんだよ。
Oh, it's nothing...
おい ２人でコソコソと怪しいな。
I think Shikamaru wants to talk
to you about something.
いや べつに なにも…。
シカマルが相談したいことが
あるみたいなんだけど。
T-Talk to me?
Maybe... next time...
we can go get a bite to eat.
そ 相談？
((今度 その なんだ…
メシでも一緒にどうだ？))
T-Talk about what?
Damn it, Choji!
そ… 相談って なんだ？
チョウジ！ お前…。
I can't come out and
say something like,
"It's no use talking to Temari
about honeymoons."
《ここで まさか→
テマリに新婚旅行の相談をしても
無理っぽいなんて言えねえよな》
Well...
I guess have no choice...
Well, you see...
まぁ… しかたねえな。
ん？
I'm seriously thinking about
a honeymoon.
いや その なんだ…。
So, if it were you,
where would you like to go?
真剣に新婚旅行について
考えてるんだがよ。
Huh?!
A-A honeymoon?!
例えば お前はどこがいいと思う？
W-What's the matter?
えぇっ!? し し し… 新婚旅行？
ど… どうした!?
N-Nothing.
A honeymoon, huh?
W-Why would you ask me that?
い… いや し… 新婚旅行か。
なんで その…
わ… 私に聞くんだ？
Huh? Well, I just figured...
えっ？ そりゃ とりあえず…。
Wait a second.
I can't come out and say
it really doesn't matter who,
《ちょっと待て…。
I just need
a woman's opinion, can I?
ここで
とりあえず 誰でもいいから→
I figured you'd be
the best one to ask.
女の意見が聞きたいなんて
いくらなんでも言えねえ》
お前に聞くのが一番かな と
思ったから だな。
I-I'm the best one?
I-I see.
わ わ… 私が い… 一番!?
O-Okay then,
I'll hear you out.
そうか… じゃあ しかたないな。
O-Oh...
ちゃんと聞こう。
お… おう！
Well, I thought a hot spring
would be nice and relaxing...
俺としては 温泉旅館なんかで
のんびりってのが→
Does that sound like something
an old man would like?
いいんじゃねえかと
考えてるんだが→
No, a hot spring sounds great!
そういうのって
じじくせぇかな？
Really? Awesome!
あ… あぁ
いいんじゃないか？ 温泉。
Good food and hot springs...
perfect, right?
そうか？ よかったぜ！
うまい飯に温泉 最高だよな！
Good. At least I got confirmation.
So now...
《よかった！ とりあえず
意見も聞けたし これで…》
Now you have to
choose where, right?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
あとは どこの旅館にするか だね。
Maybe we can check some out.
えっ？ あぁ そうだな。
簡単に下見でも行っとくか。
It's still early.
Why not go now?
Yeah, that's true. Then...
まだ 日も高いし
今から行っちゃえば？
I'm going to Amaguriama.
おう そうだな じゃあ…。
So why don't you two go?
僕は 甘栗甘に行くから
２人で行ってきなよ。
Huh?!
Sorry, I just have to have
some dessert after eating!
(テマリ/シカマル)えっ!?
う～ん ごめん 僕 どうしても
食後のデザートを食べたくてさ。
You just ate!
I always save room for dessert.
さっき 食ったじゃねえか！
You just filled that room earlier!
デザートは別腹なんだよ。
だから さっき その別腹に
しこたま入れただろ！
You idiot!
Because of Choji's big mouth,
《あぁ バカ野郎…
チョウジが勝手なこと言うから→
Temari's standing there
red-faced and upset!
テマリのやつ 怒って
顔を赤くしてるじゃねえか！》
Sorry, Choji didn't mean to
get you upset or anything.
いや その なんだ…。
Since we're talking
about honeymoons,
チョウジも悪気があって
言い出したわけじゃねえんだ。
he figured there's no sense
I go alone.
ほら… 新婚旅行だから→
Yeah, that's right.
俺１人じゃ意味がないだろう
と 思ってだな…。
A honeymoon is meant for two,
so you guys should go.
うん そうだよ。
新婚旅行なんだから
２人で行ったほうがいいよ。
Okay, you two. I'm off.
Hey, uh... Mr C-Choji?!
それじゃ お二人さん
僕は もう行くね。
What am I supposed to do now?
あっ！ チョ… チョウジさん!!
《なんつうか その…
どうすんだ？ これ！》
I'll go with you.
Huh?
行く。
へっ？
How did it turn out like this?
W-What's with this strange
nervousness?
《どうして こうなった？
なんなんだ？ この謎の緊張感は。
Anyway, I never expected
Temari to help me out
with choosing a wedding gift
for Naruto and Hinata.
とにかく ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いを→
However...
テマリが協力してくれるのは
予想外だ。
Why is she so silent
all of a sudden?
I can't get a read
on her at all!
しかし なんで
さっきから黙りっぱなしなんだ!?
First, I have to get her
out of her bad mood.
まったく読めねえ…。
W-Well... Since we're out...
まずは テマリの機嫌を
取り戻さないと！》
should we stop by
a couple places?
な… なぁ せ… せっかくだし
どっか 寄ってみるか？
O-Oh, sure...
あ… あぁ そうだな。
HIT THE TARGET
あ…。
ん？
That's rare of you to miss.
珍しいな お前が外すなんて。
What?!
あれ？
フフフッ！
Sorry...
This was all I could win.
すまねえ これしか獲れなくて。
フフッ！
I'm not completely sure,
but I think she's in
a good mood now.
《よく わかんねえが
機嫌は直ったみてぇだな》
Thank goodness!
It's still here!
I knew it was
the perfect wedding gift.
《よかった！ まだ あった。
これしかない と
思ってたんだよね！
It's cute and simple.
It's one of a kind!
かわいいし
使い勝手はよさそうだし→
I had to get money
from my savings,
なにより 一点ものだし！
but I know Hinata
will love it!
その分 貯金を下ろさなきゃ
ダメだったけど→
これなら ヒナタも
絶対 喜んでくれるはず！
Anyway, my wedding gift
to them is set!
とにかく 私からのお祝いは
これで決まり！》
I-Ino...
Imagine seeing you here.
(サクラ)あ… いのじゃない！
奇遇ね。
I can say the same about you.
そっちこそ！
こんな所で会うとはね。
– No way!
– She isn't—!
B-By the way, have you seen
Naruto lately?
《まさか…》
《こいつも…》
そ… そういえば
ナルトには 最近 会った？
No, not at all.
Imagine that,
Naruto getting married.
ううん 全然。
あのナルトが結婚だもんね！
He used to be crazy
about you long ago.
That was back when
we were kids.
昔は あんたのこと
追っかけてたのに。
I'm really happy
he and Hinata are together.
それは 子供のときの話でしょ。
There's no mistake...
ヒナタと一緒になれて
本当によかったわよ。
She's also...
– planning on that for a wedding gift!
《間違いない！》
《こいつも…》
I have to get this picture frame
before her!
《２人 : これを
結婚祝いに贈るつもりだ！》
《サクラの隙を突いて
この写真立てを手に入れなきゃ！
But how...?
Hey Sakura, were you planning
on getting this
でも どうしたら… あっ！》
あぁ サクラ…
もしかして あんた これを→
for Naruto and Hinata?
ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いにしようとか
考えてるんじゃないの？
Huh?
That's right! I have to provoke her
《そうよ
この女のプライドを挑発して→
and make her
too proud to buy it.
That's impossible, right?
買う気をなくさせればいいんだ》
You wouldn't get something
that tacky, would you?
あぁ それは ありえないか！
そんなダサい贈り物なんてね。
I'm not gonna fall for it.
This woman's trying to diss
that picture frame,
《挑発にのっちゃ ダメよ！
so I won't buy it.
この女 写真立てをディスって→
What are you talking about?
私の買う気を
削ごうとしてるだけ》
You were totally about
to buy it earlier...
何 言ってるのよ？
Th-That's...
あんただって
さっき 買おうとしてたんでしょ。
Why would you even think about
buying something tacky? How stupid!
えっ!? それは…。
ダサいと思ってるものを
わざわざ買おうとするなんて→
Stupid?!
I didn't say
I was going to buy it!
バッカじゃないの!?
バカ!?
I was just gonna move it
out of the way
私は買うなんて言ってないでしょ
そ… そうよ！
because it's trash.
邪魔なゴミだなと思って
どかそうとしただけ。
Really, you may have
brute strength,
but you have no taste at all!
ほ… ほんと あんたって
バカ力なだけで センスないわよね！
Brute strength?!
Talk about
a lame comparison!
誰が バカ力ですって!?
Excuse me!
そんな苦しい言い訳
通用するわけ ないでしょ！
You're annoying
the other customers.
あの… お客様！ 他のお客様の
ご迷惑になりますので。
See, Ino!
You're annoying the others!
You're the one who's yelling!
ほら いの！
あんたのせいで迷惑だって。
You started it!
あんたが
ギャーギャー騒いだせいでしょ！
This is mine!
元はといえば あんたでしょ！
Hey, that's mine!
I found it first!
これは 私のものよ！
私の！
Now, now...
私が 先に見つけたんじゃないの！
ちょっと！ 離しなさい!!
Please don't pull so hard,
or else—!
お客様！ そんなに すごい力で
引っ張ったら…。
– Shut up!
(２人)うるさい！
You've got some nerve!
(いの)ふざけんじゃないわよ！
Because of you,
we got kicked out!
あんたのせいで
追い出されちゃったじゃない！
That's my line!
You have no sense
of mutual compromise!
それは こっちのセリフよ！
だいたい あんたは譲り合いの精神
ってもんが ないのよ！
You have no regard for anyone,
you have no chest,
all you have is brute strength!
気がきかない 胸もない
あるのは バカ力だけ！
Huh?!
My chest has nothing
to do with this!
はぁ!?
胸は 今 関係ないでしょ！
There is nothing you
can beat me in,
so you always try to bring up
something unrelated! You should stop that.
何から何まで
私に勝てないからって→
関係ない話に
持っていこうとするのやめたら？
I don't know the meaning
of not winning.
And I win hands down
in femininity.
フン！ 勝てないとか
意味わかんない。
女らしさでは
確実に 私が勝ってますけど。
Feminine?!
You? How?
Now, now...
女らしい!? どこが？
まぁ まぁ まぁ！
Stop your fighting, you two.
Choji! Perfect timing!
２人とも ケンカはやめなよ。
チョウジ！ いいとこに来た。
Who's more feminine?
Me or Sakura?!
サクラと私
どっちが女らしいと思う？
You can't just ask something
like that out of the blue...
えっ!?
そんなの 突然 聞かれても…。
Even your own teammate, Choji,
won't pick you. How sad!
フフッ… 同じ班だったチョウジに
ひいきされない時点で→
Huh?!
Choji's not on your team,
悲しすぎるじゃない。
はぁ!?
but he won't even try to
flatter you. That is so sad!
違う班のチョウジに お世辞すら
言ってもらえない時点で→
H-Hey, cut it out.
痛すぎるでしょ！
ちょ ちょ ちょ… やめてよ。
Hmm... Okay then...
If you want to know,
why don't you put it to a test.
じゃあさ そんなに知りたいなら
試してみればいいじゃない？
– A test?
Personally, I think someone who
can cook is very feminine.
(２人)試す？
僕だったら 料理作れる人のほうが
女らしいって考えちゃうね。
So maybe you should see
who cooks better?
だから 料理を比べてみれば
いいんじゃない？
Okay, let's begin
the challenge!
The one who makes
the tastiest food pills wins.
それじゃあ
勝負を始めましょう。
より おいしい兵糧丸を
作ったほうが 勝利よ。
You just watch, Sakura.
I know what you like
and dislike.
《見てなさい サクラ！
こっちは あんたの好き嫌いは
お見通し。
I just have to make something
that'll make you gag.
あんたが ギャフンと言うものを作れば
私の勝ちよ》
The judge will be Choji.
Huh?! You're not going
to eat it?!
審査は チョウジに任せるわ。
Fine with me!
えっ!?
あんたが食べるんじゃないの？
I just ate a mountain
of ice cream,
大丈夫 僕は山ほど
アイスを食べてきたばかりだけど→
but I always have room
for food pills!
兵糧丸は別腹だから。
W-Wait!
Choji's my teammate.
ま 待ってよ
チョウジは私の班だったんだし→
That gives me the edge!
You should be okay with
having the advantage...
これじゃあ
私に有利でしょ？
なに？ 自分が有利なら
それでいいはずじゃない。
Don't tell me...
You weren't planning to poison them
to make me sick, were you?
まさか 私を ダウンさせるために→
毒でも入れるんじゃ
ないでしょうね？
Like I would!
Come on, let's get started!
何にもないわよ
さあ 早く始めましょう。
Okay, without further ado!
The food pill contest to see
who's more feminine, begins!
では早速 どっちが女らしいか
兵糧丸対決…。
Ready, fight!
レディー ファイト！
Whoa, what's this?!
Instead of using
a mortar and pestle,
(チョウジ)おおっと これは！
she uses her
fine chakra control
あえて すり鉢など使わず
微妙なチャクラコントロールで→
to get the ingredients
to the desired size.
素材の大きさに
変化をつけている。
I can't wait to taste
the sensation
when I put it in my mouth!
口に入れたときの食感が
楽しみだよ～！
Whoa!
She's searing the ingredients
with super-fire power!
うほ～！ 超火力で
一気に素材を加熱している！
Sakura is using some
legendary golden honey.
サクラが使っているのは
幻の黄金ハチミツ！
Ino is using cacao powder.
Both seem irresistible!
いのは カカオパウダーか
どっちも捨てがたい！
Th-This is...?!
こ これは！
Th-This is...
こ これは…。
Yummy!
うお～ うまっ！
So delicious!
う～ ま～ い～ よ～！
Rich, yet not too overpowering...
That indescribable something
このまったりとして
しつこくなく→
that explodes when
it hits your tongue...
That delicate aroma
and taste that lingers...
舌の上で シャッキリポンと
はじけながらも→
上品な香りの中に
転がるような後味は→
It's a treasure chest
of sweetness!
まさに 甘さの宝石箱だよ！
Choji!
So? Which is it?
チョウジ！
で どっちなの？
Which one tastes better?
Oh, I wolfed both down,
so I can't tell.
どっちが
おいしいのよ！
あ いっぺんに食べちゃったから
わかんないや。
But they were both really... good...
でも どっちも
すごくおいしい。
い い… うっ ぶは～！
– Choji!
Choji! Choji!
(２人)チョウジ！
(いの)チョウジ チョウジ！
I've made a lot of friends too.
《僕にも 仲間がいっぱい
できたよ！》
Noooo!
Choji! Don't die!
いや～！
チョウジ 死なないで～！
What's happening?
Is his life flashing
before his eyes?
なんなの これ
走馬灯 走馬灯なの!?
Ino!
You did use poison,
didn't you?!
いの やっぱり
毒入れたわね？
You know I wouldn't!
Just who do
you think I am, anyway?!
そんなもん入れるか！
あんた 私を何だと思ってるのよ！
I've made... a lot of friends...
仲間がいっぱい… できたよ。
This is bad!
Choji's delirium is getting worse!
まずいわ チョウジの走馬灯が
２周目に突入したわよ！
What are you doing?
I have to see what's inside it
before I can treat him.
どうする気？
何が入っているのか
確かめてみないことには→
If there's poison in it,
my tongue will go numb...
治療のしようがないわ！
毒が入っていたら
舌が痺れるかもしれないけど。
I told you,
there's no poison inside!
だから毒なんて
入ってないってば！
Damn it!
あ～ もう！
It's delicious!
Uh-huh!
Why?
おいしい！
うん。
I really love this taste.
なんで…
私 この味 すっごく好き！
Me too! I love this flavor!
Boy, that surprised me.
私も この味 大好き！
いや～ びっくりしたよ。
I ate too many sweets...
Seems my blood sugar
shot up.
甘いもの食べ過ぎて…。
血糖値が大変なことに
なっちゃったみたい。
But I'm okay now!
Is that all?
でも もう大丈夫。
なんだ よかった。
Thank goodness.
Hey, Ino.
Why would you go out of the way
to make something I love?
ねえ いの なんでわざわざ
私の好きな味にしたの？
Well...
I figured if I surprised you with
a flavor you'd love, I'd win.
そりゃあ
あんたの好きな味で→
ギャフンと言わせれば
勝てると思って。
What, really?
That was my strategy too!
はあ 何それ？
私と同じ作戦じゃない。
Huh?! You too?
No wonder
I love how it tastes!
え？ じゃあ サクラも？
どうりで
私が好きな味だったわけだ。
(２人)フフフ！
Ultimately, we saw right
through each other.
結局 お互いのこと
お見通しだったわけね。
Okay, since we know
each other so well,
there's something
I want to say to you.
それじゃあ お見通しついでに
言いたいことがあるんだけど。
What is it?
Don't you think we'd find
something even better
なによ？
if we looked for
a wedding gift together?
私たち２人で
結婚祝いを探せば→
もっといいものが
見つけられると思わない？
What now?
ウフフ アハハ！
なによ。
I was thinking the same thing.
それも お見通しだから。
TOMIYA
That inn seems nice.
Huh?
あの旅館よさそうだな。
え？
I'd better hurry up
and choose or
《シカマル : さっさと決めねえと→
I'll just keep mulling over
this wedding gift.
ずっと結婚祝いのことで
ウダウダ悩んじまうぞ。
I just have to pick something!
思い切って腹くくるしかねえ》
Okay. Let's go in!
Huh?!
よし 入るぞ！
ええ～！
What's the matter?
Weren't we just going to...
look around?
どうした？
これは 下見じゃないのか？
Yeah, but we have to go inside
or we can't make a decision.
下見だけどよ でも入ってみねえと
決心つかねえだろ。
No, but...
I'm not mentally prepared...
いや しかし
まだ 心の準備が…。
What? Mentally prepared?
Is she panicking because
this place too fancy?
《なんだ 心の準備？
あまりに豪華な旅館で
ビビってんのか？》
It's okay.
Temari, let's just go inside
and then we can decide.
大丈夫だって とりあえず
入ってから考えよう な？
I-It'll be too late once
we go inside!
I might get caught up
in the mood...
入ってからだと遅いんだ！
雰囲気にながされて
しまうかもしれないから。
What's she talking about?
The mood?
《どういうことだ 雰囲気？
The mood of that inn?
What does she mean
by getting caught up in it?
あの旅館の雰囲気がどうした？
I don't get it!
それに流されるってなんだ？
さっぱりわからねえ》
Hey... you don't...
お前 まさか！
... have a fever, do you?
熱でもあるんじゃねえか？
I-I'm going home!
わ 私は先に帰るからな！
H-Hey, wait!
It's gonna get dark soon!
おい待て じきに暗くなるぞ！
If you're not feeling well,
we really should book
a room and rest!
体調も悪いなら なおさら→
宿でもとって
休んでかなくちゃなんねえだろ！
Please wait!
I really... need you!
待ってくれ！
俺には お前が必要なんだ！
Are you sure... I'm the one?
本当に私でいいのか？
Yeah! You're the only one!
ああ お前しかいない！
Besides, I can't go into
the women's bath.
なんつったって 俺じゃ
女湯に入れないからな。
What?
Temari, I need you to go
into the women's bath
え？
テマリ お前が女湯に入って→
and report back
every detail to me.
俺に女湯の様子を
こと細かく報告してくれ。
That's all. Easy, right?
ただ それだけでいいんだ
な？ 簡単だろ？
So, uh...
Just what is this all
about anyway?
というか
これは いったい何の話だ？
What else? I'm going
to gift Naruto and Hinata
何って ナルトとヒナタの
結婚祝いで贈る→
a honeymoon for
their wedding gift,
and I need to choose the inn.
新婚旅行の
旅館選びに決まってんだろ。
Oh... So that's it.
ふ～ん そうだったのか。
Huh? Didn't I... tell you?
え？
言ってなかったっけ？
This is the first
I've heard about it.
ああ 初耳だ。
ええっ ぎゃ～！
ICHIRAKU RAMEN
So, you're back to square one
in your search for
a wedding gift?
それじゃあ また
結婚祝い探しなおすんだ。
Yeah...
But I think it turned out
for the best.
うん まあでも
これで よかった気がする。
What about you, Shikamaru?
で シカマルは何があったの？
Trying to explain
everything is a drag...
説明するのも面倒くせえ。
(イルカ)ハハハ…。
22 MORE DAYS UNTIL THE WEDDING
kakaeta omou i tokitoshite
Sometimes, the feelings we have
kazoe kirenai itami o
Cause us immense pain
yuzurenai hokori mune ni
We've lived this entire time
imamade ikite kitadarou
With unshakeable pride in our hearts
tatakau koto de mamotte
Defending by fighting
omoigakenaku nakushite
With unexpected losses
kizutsukiai ma nande
We learn as we hurt one another
taisetsu na koto ni kizukudarou
Will we realize what's most important?
koe ga todokanai
My voice cannot reach you
soredemo (soredemo)
Even so
kokoro shinjite iyou
Let's trust our hearts
zenshin zenrei kimi wo mamoru yo
I will protect you with every essence of my being
towa ni sou towa ni
For all eternity
nankaidatte tachiagare yo
Stand up again and again
sono ishi de (sono ishi de)
By your own volition
ungai souten asu wo egaku yo
Don't give in; create a new day
tomo ni sou tomo ni
Together with friends
itsudatte akirameru
Never ever give up
na michi wo hirakou
Let's open up the path
ruru
On and on
It's Naruto's wedding!
Hinata's madly in love!
I'm jealous! Fool, ya fool!
The wedding gift, I gotta prepare...
For those two,
something extravagant.
If it's too expensive,
let's split it!
This makes me
wanna get married too!
I can do it!
I'll be the next one up!
I'm so popular,
I'm on the verge of bursting!
For real... I'm on the frontlines
of romance!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Hidden Leaf Story,
The Perfect Day for a Wedding,
Part 3: The Kazekage's Wedding Gift"